touristlink.com 2016-03-05

# Touristlink :: Privacy Policy

This privacy policy covers all the users of the Touristlink.com website. We are committed to respecting your privacy. This privacy statement sets forth how www.Touristlink.com uses the information its users provide when using the website. We are committed to ensuring that our user's information is protected. The information you provide us will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. You, the customer, can help us ensure your privacy by not providing your user name or password to anyone.

What we collect
    When registering with us, we may collect the following information from you such as: 

  * Full name
  * Contact information, including e-mail address
  * Other information relevant to surveys/promotional offers

What we do with the information we collect
    We will use the following personal information in order to provide you with the travel offers & promotion from our site and provide our members with outstanding service as we continue to improve our own content and services. 

We send update emails to our members from time to time, to keep them up to date with new destinations, promotions, and site news. Members and non-members are subject to the same privacy policies. Members can opt-out of these emails at the time of registration, or by going to the url "[unsubscribe](http://www.touristlink.com/newsletter/cancelsubscription.html "unsubscribe")", or by replying to the original email with the word " **unsubscribe** " in the subject line, or by emailing [support@touristlink.com](mailto:support@touristlink.com). We may ask our members additional information when they sign up. Additionally, we may solicit feedback from our customers. When you provide feedback or send inquiries to us, we may retain those   
communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

**In addition to the above, we use the information that you provide us in the following ways:**

  * We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Our members will, from time to time, receive information on tourist destination, services, special deals, and a newsletter.
  * We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account. We reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.
  * We will use your IP (Internet Protocol) address to assist us in diagnosing problems with our server as well as administering our website. Additionally, we use your IP address to help suggest you the matching destination and friend, and to gather broad demographic information about who our users are.

Cookies
     Cookies are small bits of text used by a browser to store information on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. When you visit our website, we send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, this may prevent you from taking full advantage of our website.
  
Other Sites
    This privacy policy only covers our website, at www.touristlink.com. Our website may contain links to other websites. Note that we do not have any control over other website once you leave our website and we are not responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites. Other sites may have privacy policies that differ from ours.
  
Data Collection by Conversion Tracking
     This site uses a cookie to measure advertising performance as we have opted in to conversion tracking on Google and its AdSense partners websites.The conversion tracking cookie is set when a user clicks on an ad delivered by Google where we have opted in to tracking. These cookies expire within 30 days and are not personally identifiable. If this cookie has not yet expired when the user visits certain pages of this website, Google and Lark will be able to tell that the user clicked the ad and proceeded to that page. Each advertiser gets a different cookie, so no cookie can be tracked across advertiser websites.  

  * How we use the conversion cookie information. We use the information collected by the conversion cookie to provide aggregate conversion stats. We are able to see the total number of users who have clicked on our ad and proceeded to a page tagged with a conversion tracking tag, but they do not have access to personally identifying information.
  * How to opt out of the conversion cookie. If you want to disable conversion tracking cookies, you can set your browser to block cookies from the googleadservices.com domain.

SSL Security Features
     This website takes every precaution to protect our user's information. During data transmission, we use Secured Sockets layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information that you input. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personally identifiable customer information. 
  
Log Files 
    Like many other Web sites, www.touristlink.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 
  
Cookies and Web Beacons 
    www.touristlink.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 
  
Doubleclick Dart Cookie 

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.touristlink.com.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.touristlink.com and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .... Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.touristlink.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.touristlink.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.touristlink.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

Contacting TouristLink about Privacy Policy 
    If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy policy, please send us an e-mail at [support@touristlink.com](mailto:support@touristlink.com). Additionally, we encourage you to check our website from time to time as we may update and modify our privacy policy. 

Attn: Privacy Officer  
Touristlink.com  
Holiday Deals Pvt Ltd. / Touristlink Corp

14/1 & 14/2, 2nd Floor, IT Park  
South Ambazari Road,Parsodi,  
Nagpur, MH 440022  
India

or [Contact Us](http://www.touristlink.com/contactus.html "Contact Us")  
Last updated June 6, 2013
